So, hello everyone, in this video we are going to work with our signup page.
So, in the previous video there was some error I guess, okay.
So it was in authorstore.js actually.
I was thinking of toast.error, that is why it was showing error, but since I am using
error.message, so this error should be used like this error.message, okay.
So fix this and after this we are going to work with this signup.txt, okay.
So at the beginner files for all the styles, I have just written here, okay.
And if you are going to just preview it, so you will see like this, the signup page,
and if you click on the login page, you will get this login page, okay.
So it is consistent, it has a linear gradient, I have fixed everything.
So now, we are going to work with this signup page, right.
So let's go to this signup page, so it would be in the front end folder only.
So front end we have this signup page.
And the first thing which we are going to do is, we are going to import one hook from react,
which is import use a state, use state from react, okay.
So we have imported this, use state from react.
And now we are going to define this bunch of variables here.
And along with that, we are also going to set those values.
So const, so it would be username, comma set username, username set username equal to
use a state, so it would be use a state, and then we are going to get this and now const, again,
email comma set email, okay, email comma set email equals to use state.
You state, we are going to assign this a blank value as of now, now const, pass word and set
password equal to use a state, and then assign this as blank values, okay.
So first initial values would be like blank only, right.
And since now we are, what we have to do, we have to change the values like whenever
the values if you see, okay.
So we are going to change the values, so we have this label class name username,
and whenever the input would be like we have type equal to text, right.
So now in this one, we will have value, okay.
So value would be the username, okay.
So value would be the username in case of username, and if you are changing the thing,
like on change equals to, if you are making any change in this input field, then in that case,
the set user name would be called and it will have e.target.value, okay.
So now after this, this is done.
So now we are going to do the same thing for this class name for email address.
So now what we are going to do is like for this one, we have value equal to username,
on change equal to e.target.value, copy both of these values and paste it here.
So here the value would be, so the value would be email,
value is email, and set email, okay.
And after this, we have this password and set password, so the same thing would be here.
So paste this, so the type would be password, value equal to password,
password, and on change e.set password, so let us go to this website, see we can make the change,
so as more codes, anything and the password. So this is happening with the help of the user state,
okay. So user state is going to set all this, like whenever we are making a dynamic change,
we are making a change in this input field. So the set, the states are going to accept all the
value and through this, it is going to change like the value is password, and this set password
is setting the password, like e.target.value, so whenever the event is going to happen,
like event is what, typing in the input field, okay. So in that case, it is going to accept the value,
and it is going to call this set password function, and whenever you type the like keys,
so it is going to change, so that's why it is on change equal to e set password, so
this e is actually event, so event.target.value. So one more thing, like there is one more function
const handle submit, so we are also going to submit the form right to submit equals to e,
and then we are going to use this function prevent default. So make sure to,
like whenever you are submitting a form, it should not like re render it, okay. So here you can see
the form here, so the form, and we are going to use the function here, so on submit,
on submit equals to, we are going to just assign this handle submit here, okay. So control is safe,
so this is all for this video, we are going to see with another one in the next video.